Ryan Degen

Game Developer

12 St Denis Street, Oromocto, NB E2V 1Z3 (613) 401-9998 ryandegen.dev@gmail.com

SKILLS

I've worked in Unreal, made my own engine in C++, made games for game jams in Lua, and used GitHub to store all of it. However my best skills are in C#, Unity, Unity Services and Unity Version Control, along with my excellent teamwork having come from working on Unity projects that have many developers at once, and navigating the Version Control without issue while doing it.

EXPERIENCE

Reframe Games, Remote - *Game Developer (Summer Contract)*July 2024 - August 2024

- Created and prototyped different concepts in Unity
- Worked on porting desktop games to mobile, and console.
- Worked specifically on player abilities, and movement.
- Made a spring algorithm to improve game feel

Reframe Games, Remote - Intern

March 2024- July 2024

- Created demos for Unity games
- Worked with many others at the same time using Unity Version Control.
- Made online multiplayer functionality, with a joining code system.
- Designed levels for a 2D Pixel platformer

EDUCATION

Eastern College, Remote- Video Game Development

October 2022 - July 2024

Graduated from Eastern College with distinction, for getting a 95%, learned Math and Physics for game development here, along with making my own engine, using Unreal and Unity, and making my own website.

James Madison High School, Remote- High School Diploma

September 2021 - July 2022

Graduated from James Madison High with honors, got a 3.70 GPA, most relevant courses here were Math and Physics.